<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Reputations>
  <Reputation>
    <Key>GUARDBELOVED</Key>
    <Name>Beloved</Name>
    <Description>[H4]Beloved[h4]
      Add [BO][BO][BO] to Charm and Negotiation checks. Add [SE][SE][SE] to Coercion checks.
      The PC may spend a Destiny Point to follow the will of the Force to a person or place in need of defense. Unfamiliar NPCs frequently come to the Guardian with requests for help, usually related to the Guardian's specialization or most famous abilities.
      The Guardian occasionally detects secret Force-using individuals, though they do not always detect the Gardian's abilities.
      If the Guardian displays Force powers in public, the ISB or cabals of other Force users investigate immediately. 
      Imperial Inquisitors might seek to find and vanquish the Guardian, having heard whispers of the character's prowess and virtue.</Description>
    <Source Page="92">Keeping the Peace source book</Source>
    <Level>3</Level>
  </Reputation>
  <Reputation>
    <Key>GUARDRENOWNED</Key>
    <Name>Renowned</Name>
    <Description>[H4]Renowned[h4]
      Add [BO][BO] to Charm and Negotiation checks. Add [SE][SE] to Coercion checks.
      The PC may spend a Destiny Point to follow the will of the Force to a person or place in need of defense. Unfamiliar NPCs frequently come to the Guardian with requests for help.
      The ISB or cabals of other Force users occasionally investigate stories of the PC.
      If the Guardian displays Force powers in public, ISB agents might seek to capture the Guardian based on resulting reports of the character's mystical abilities</Description>
    <Source Page="92">Keeping the Peace source book</Source>
    <Level>2</Level>
  </Reputation>
  <Reputation>
    <Key>GUARDRESPECTED</Key>
    <Name>Respected</Name>
    <Description>[H4]Respected[h4]
      Add [BO][BO] to Charm and Negotiation checks. Add [SE][SE] to Coercion checks.</Description>
    <Source Page="92">Keeping the Peace source book</Source>
    <Level>1</Level>
  </Reputation>
  <Reputation>
    <Key>GUARDNEUTRAL</Key>
    <Name>Neutral</Name>
    <Description>[H4]Neutral[h4]
      Whether due to anonymity or a conflicted past marked by great deeds both cruel and kind, people are not inclined to either fear or trust the reputation of the Guardian (as always, add [BO] and [SE] as usual based on individual interactions and histories between the PC and other characters).</Description>
    <Source Page="92">Keeping the Peace source book</Source>
    <Level>0</Level>
  </Reputation>
  <Reputation>
    <Key>GUARDFEARED</Key>
    <Name>Feared</Name>
    <Description>[H4]Feared[h4]
      Add [BO][BO] to Coercion checks. Add [SE][SE] to Charm and Negotiation checks.</Description>
    <Source Page="92">Keeping the Peace source book</Source>
    <Level>-1</Level>
  </Reputation>
  <Reputation>
    <Key>GUARDNOTORIOUS</Key>
    <Name>Notorious</Name>
    <Description>[H4]Notorious[h4]
      Add [BO][BO] to Coercion checks. Add [SE][SE] to Charm and Negotiation checks. 
      The PC may spend a Destiny Point to have an uninvolved individual overlook one of his misdeeds out of fear of his dark reputation.
      The ISB or cabals of other Force users occasionally investigate stories of the PC.
      If the Guardian displays Force powers in public, ISB agents might seek to capture the Guardian based on resulting reports of the character's mystical abilities.</Description>
    <Source Page="92">Keeping the Peace source book</Source>
    <Level>-2</Level>
  </Reputation>
  <Reputation>
    <Key>GUARDDREADED</Key>
    <Name>Dreaded</Name>
    <Description>[H4]Dreaded[h4]
      Add [BO][BO][BO] to Coercion checks. Add [SE][SE][SE] to Charm and Negotiation checks. 
      The PC may spend a Destiny Point to have an uninvolved individual overlook one of his misdeeds or to cause a single minion NPC to flee in terror from an encounter with him because of the dark deeds the Guardian is rumored to have carried out.
      If the Guardian displays Force powers in public, the ISB or cabals of other Force users investigate immediately.
      Imperial Inquisitors might seek to find and vanquish (or recruit) the Guardian, having heard whispers of the character's terrible power.</Description>
    <Source Page="92">Keeping the Peace source book</Source>
    <Level>-3</Level>
  </Reputation>
</Reputations>